♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
What can Yumi be doing?
We have to get somedata out of sector five!
It’s not like her to be late.
Maybe she’s with William.
I said maybe.
By the way, Jeremie, have you made any
headway on the anti virus recently?
Well…
Actually, it’s going kind of slow. I’m missing a lot of important codes.
But with a little luck, we’ll find them today.
And then, it’s ciao XANA!
We’ll finally be able to shut down the supercomputer.
We better forget about Yumi. I’m transferring you.
Transfer Odd.
Transfer Aelita.
Transfer Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Aelita.
Virtualization!
Now, head for the edge of the sector, okay?
Oh, there you are!
Hi, Jeremie. Sorry, I--
Hurry up. I’ll tell them to wait for you.
Virtualization!
A little longer, and we would’ve started the party without you.
Where were you?
I had something to do.
Yeah, right, like being with William.
Huh? Hey, don’t you get tired of being jealous all the time?
Aha, I knew it! You were with him!
You can believe whatever you want.
Be a jerk if you want, too.
You must think I’m really dumb.
Careful, you have visitors.
Hey, settle this later, okay?
I’m gonna give them a little Odd acupuncture.
Aelita, take cover.
Laser arrow!
One down! Great way to start off the morning.
Watch it! More Kankrelats at five o'clock!
Pretty interesting welcoming committee.
What do you expect?
XANA hates it when we go fishing in Sector Five!
Two more!
Laser arrow!
Oh no! The Scyphozoa!
Hm?
Huh?
Yumi!
Yumi, are you okay?
I don’t know, I feel kind of funny.
Well anyway, it seems to have scared the Kankrelats away.
Why would they go after you? We’ll abort the mission!
Materialization Yumi!
Materialization Odd!
Materialization Aelita!
You must’ve tripped on your fingers, Einstein. Yumi isn’t here.
Huh?
J-Jeremie? Is something wrong?
Uh… no, I must’ve made a mistake, I’ll reboot the program!
Materialization Ulrich!
Materialization Yumi!
Missed again.
I can’t believe it.
Yumi, I don’t know what’s going on, I can’t devirtualize you!
What?
Go and hide in a tower while I figure this out!
Direction is south southeast!
Don’t worry, I’ll find the bug. You’re safe in the tower.
It’s not XANA I’m worried about, Jeremie. It’s the principal.
Huh?
Oh no, I almost forgot! Today’s the class picture!
What class picture?
Hello, the ninth grade picture?
It’s this morning!
One day suspension for any unjustified absence. Thanks a lot, Delmas.
Can you just picture my parents’ faces if I get suspended?
I’ll do all I can, Yumi, I promise.
Hey, I have an idea. You know what a great actor I am, right?
With a wig, a dress, and a little make-up, I could take your place in the photo
and bam! Signed, sealed, and delivered.
Signed, sealed, and suspended is more like it.
No way.
Hang on a second, huh? That’s not a bad idea!
There! You see? Ulrich finally admits that I’m a great actor!
You? You stink.
Huh?
But I know a really great actress.
Hi, Sissi. Say, can I talk to you for a second?
Uh, well, yeah, of course.
I have something really important to ask you.
Who, me?
And in exchange, I’m ready to do whatever you want.
Anything?
Well, almost anything.
In my opinion, when the Scyphozoa attacked you,
he gave you some kind of bug, Yumi.
Could it have stolen some of my memory?
That’s strange, it’s my memory
that XANA seems to be after!
If you ask me, the Scyphozoa took something else from you.
Stand still, I’m launching a digital analysis.
Oh no! I don’t believe it!
What’s the matter?
The Scyphozoa stole the sequence code for your human DNA!
What’s that?
Well, when you’re virtualized, you
keep your human DNA sequence code.
You can’t do without it. It defines
your molecular structure, which is the--
Okay, okay, just get to the point!
No DNA, no way to get back to Earth.
Oh no!
I’m listening.
Well, since Yumi can’t be here this morning
I’d like you to stand in for her in
the ninth grade class photo.
Okay.
Huh? You… you’ll do it? And, um…
what do you want in exchange?
Oh, what do you think I am? I don’t want anything at all.
Just call it a personal favor to you and that’s that.
Oh, this can’t be true. What about my parents,
and school, and my brother?
You have to find a solution, Jeremie.
My whole life is on Earth!
Don’t panic, Yumi. I’ll do everything I can.
What if--
You have an idea?
I think so. Send me to Lyoko.
What are you gonna do?
Just trust me this time.
Alright, I’ll bring you up close to the tower.
A quarter of an hour to put on a dress
and a wig, unbelieveable.
There you go, what do you think?
Not bad. The hair looks like Yumi’s.
Yeah, but she doesn’t dress like that.
She always wears black,
and her dresses are longer and less…
Less sexy?
Well, why don’t you bring me one of her dresses?
Right, good idea, we’ll try.
Sissi’s being strangely helpful.
Yeah, I suppose. Weird, huh?
Cool, it’s open, I’m in! Piece of cake! Warn me if you see anyone coming.
I read you loud and clear, General!
Okay, Aelita, the tower is nearby at ten o’clock.
I’ll have another Shiro-An.
You did a very good job on the white bean paste.
You know, Takeo,
I’ve been feeling depressed lately.
You don’t pay any attention to me.
It’s almost as if you don’t listen to me anymore.
Mmmm, delicious.
Oh, sorry, what were you saying?
Watch out for monsters!
Aelita, now will you tell me what your idea is?
No!
It’s always the same thing. My mother warned
me not to marry a man from Tokyo.
Bingo!
Aelita, please tell me what you’re up to.
There. Process launched.
What process?
The process of transferring my DNA
sequence code to your virtual structure.
What? Are you crazy?
Jeremie, Yumi’s place is on Earth.
If anyone should stay on Lyoko
until we find a solution, it’s me.
I don’t agree with that! Aelita, stop it--
I knew he was going to say that.
You know, you’re making a big sacrifice, Aelita.
Call it whatever you want to.
Aelita, do you hear me?
Aelita! I can’t believe this!
I don’t even know how that kind of transfer works!
Oh no! This is unbelieveable!
Okay.
I’ll go and wake Hiroki.
(PHONE RINGS)
Yumi?
Darling? Have you seen Yumi?
No, she must’ve left for school already.
Oh, she forgot her cell phone!
Odd!
Odd, is that how you stand guard?
I didn’t see anybody go by
You got the dress?
(PHONE RINGS)
Jeremie, Sorry. I didn’t mean to
hang up on you, but it was either
that or getting caught by Yumi’s mom.
Listen to me, Aelita is on Lyoko, transferring her
DNA sequence code over to Yumi.
Uh? So what? you mean that’s not a good idea?
No, Aelita doesn’t know that when she transfers
her code over, her memory will be exposed.
What?
Are you saying that Xana will just
be able to steal it at will?
That’s right, I’m sure that’s why
the Scyphozoa attacked Yumi.
It’s another one of Xana’s little evil schemes .
Then warn Aelita, tell her to stop.
I can’t, she’s cut off all
communication with the tower.
So you’ve got to get to Lyoko fast.
Ok, I wouldn’t exactly call it glamorous, but it
will do, you can count on me.
Thanks Sissi.
I owe you one.
Only ten more minutes before the transfer.
Everything will be just fine.
Girls! You leave em alone for five minutes,
and it’s mess after mess after mess.
Jeremie! Warm up the scanners,
we’re on our way.
Transfer Ulrich.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Virtualization!
Hey Yumi! I was looking for you
in the schoolyard this morning.
Hey, wait, who are you?
That’s the principle’s Daughter, it’s Elizabeth.
Too weird.
Listen, first of all, the name is Sissi, and
second of all, just shut up. Ok?
Ok, Elizabeth.
(SMACK)
(LAUGHTER)
Ow, that hurt!
You should be able to spot the tower now.
There it is!
We’ll be there in a minute!
Just one more minute.
Hurry up, hurry up!
Aelita! Stop right now!
If the transfer takes place,
Xana will steal all of your memory.
Aelita! Stop everything right now!
Huh?
Phew
Jeremie?
Aelita, you’re so stubborn, that was a silly thing to do!
I’m sorry, but I thought I was doing the right thing.
I understand, and I appreciate it too.
You’re turning into a real human being.
You’re beginning to confuse generosity with stupidity.
Anyway, we still have no idea how to save Yumi.
Don’t bet on that, I just happen to have a brilliant idea!
Xana has stolen Yumi’s DNA code sequence,
so it must be in his memory.
And how do we get access to Xana’s memory?
Sector Five!
Why are you dressed up to look like Yumi?
It’s none of your business.
Anyways, that dumb haircut of
yours is really old fashioned.
I never look old fashioned. understand?
Everything looks fashionable on me.
Ugh, it’s a good thing I didn’t eat breakfast this morning.
Quiet down!
He’s right, shut up, will you?
What’s all this noise about?
Yumi, is anything wrong?
Yumi, I’m speaking to you.
Sissi?
I can explain everything, daddy, darling.
Daddy, darling, daddy, darling, daddy.
(LAUGHTER)
That’s enough.
Uh, by the way Yumi, just a little detail.
Without your Human DNA sequence code,
you’re just as vulnerable as Aelita.
If you get hit, you’ll disappear forever.
Great.
Come On, let’s go.
The countdown has started! You have
three minutes to get out of the core zone!
First, we have to find the key.
Check at the end of the corridor
I spotted the mechanism on the wall at the end of the room.
Yes, I see it over there.
Looks like a trap to me, but when
you gotta go, you gotta go.
Odd!
Watch out!
The whole ceiling is boobytrapped, move it!
Faster guys! You’ve got one minute left to turn the key!
Move it!
Timber!
Odd!
Huh?
Odd, are you ok?
Well--
Ok.
Good work, Ulrich.
After you, ladies.
Here comes our taxi.
We’d better not miss it.
Now!
Aelita, do you know where to find
Yumi’s DNA sequence code?
Not really, but I’ll manage somehow.
A Flying Mantas nest is about to hatch, we don’t have much time left.
Uh, Yumi, I wanted to apologise for this morning. It was none of my business what you've been doing.
That’s true, but I’ll tell you anyway.
I was buying two tickets for the Subsonics concert.
And it wasn’t easy! Bad internet connection.
Lookout, the nest just hatched!
How’s it going, Aelita?
Nothing yet.
That’s it, I’ve got it!
I’m sending it to you now, Jeremie.
I’ve got it, Yumi.
I’ll download it back to you in a second.
I’m gonna be really happy to go home--
Yumi!
Did you have time to reinsert the code?
I sure hope so.
You two get outta there.
The north tunnel, it’s open!
Yumi?
It’s ok, don’t worry, she’s out
cold, but she’s here with us.
How about you, Odd?
How you feeling?
Ever been flattened by a steamroller?
No.
It’s simple, just get yourself
devirtualized in sector five.
Your father caught you?
Aw, am I going to get suspended?
Don’t worry, I saved your day.
I’ll get punished, but not you.
Anyway, I know how to talk to my father.
Here. Here’s your dress back.
That uh-- That was really nice of you, Sissi.
Yeah, she’s right, thankyou.
I told you you could count on me.
See ya later.
Sissi, uh, wait.
How would you like to see the Subsonics with Ulrich?
Are you kidding?
Great!
Something’s really fishy about the
way Sissi’s behaving.
Maybe, deep down she’s a very nice person.
Or she’s really crazy about Ulrich.
What a mess.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BYREDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO